all righty today's city challenge to set
up St fre andfor stores unintimidating
and take down
limit this sounds
fun take down limit and
unintimidating which means I'm going to
have to just knock people out including
the camera
operator and we can't even take everyone
out in this
case s that was incredibly ambitious and
also there is no it's actually perfect
I'll knock this guard out and I keep it
and then afterwards we'll go figure out
what's happening so cyber's going to
actually lockpick that open and disable
the window alarms because that's kind of
how this works and then afterwards we'll
go upstairs but actually we'll start by
avoiding that
camera that's not how sure that works I
mean I'm not going to complain about it
but it's definitely questionable to some
extent so now we're going to do is wait
for
cyber and that got to leave no we're not
doing that
guard if you could there we go and all
I'm got to do is lock why am I lock
picking this
one there there is
literally all right we'll lockpick this
one too why not right that g might
actually cause us some Pro right then
we're not doing that I'm just going to
go down here and I'm going to go past
all of this and I'm going to go over
here and see if it's a camera
operator it is not the camera operator
this is the safe room that is not that
useful right then
maybe don't check this first since this
is the way I'm doing it is rather dumb
too and of course there a guard here at
just the perfect time right then we're
checking upstairs
first I mean I probably could
have you're joking and also cyber why do
you have a guard with a radio over there
you're supposed to wait you know what
it's fine we'll go back down and shy
this we're going back up
all right we'll wait for this one go
on there we go and we
will
right you'll be fine this is the server
room we are going downstairs
okay let's go over here and then
afterwards we're going through this door
and then afterwards we
will yeah it's not going to work
hack the cameras and afterwards we'll
grab the key card and then hopefully we
don't walk into a bunch of God when we
leave this
room almost did right then now all we
got to do is figure out what we're doing
with literally everything here so we'll
start by searching these fouls and
hopefully it goes
well
hopefully it probably
won't it's not of course it's not why
would it be those far specifically on
the first
sorry I'm going to do something really
dumb and it's going to
work all right unless us don't walk
downstairs right right we're we're done
I made that God stop this isn't this is
not even funny anymore don't walk
towards me good walk no absolutely
not I'm GNA play a game right I'm going
to walk and I'm going to finish that
and it's not it that was literally not
worth it at all it it literally was not
worth it at
all right then we'll open up this door I
literally have a key card why am I
scrambling it well cyber is going to
find a last fou
right right right then we're going
downstairs again to find the last foul
is it
over good one cyber great one
right then
let's actually this is perfect you look
over here right don't pay too much
attention and I will search these fows
and you will not cause me any problems
right okay okay no you keep staring in
this direction don't cause me any more
problems and I will finally finish
searching these
FS don't
[Music]
you know that was risky but I'm happy
that it worked I'm going to go search
the servers so we're not going to have
any more of these problems and we're
actually going to use the key card so
that that gu does not attack me now
right then we'll set up this connection
and then afterwards we're going to go
open the
safe and cyber's going to go plant The
Trackers over
there right then let's go
down and at this rate cyber's going to
be upstairs faster than I can be
downstairs so we'll run through all of
this maybe not the best idea but it'll
be fine and will open up this
save and I assume cyber's going to join
us recently
soon
right right
then we'll grab this cash and we'll get
out of
here where is
cyber you know what it's fine camera
operator ST which means door alarms
won't cause us any problems which means
I can just run out of there through the
front door and that's the da CH in just
under 5 minutes and 15 seconds I mean
unintimidating and take down limit is a
definitely intimidating combination but
it's not exactly horrible either just a
small change of tactics cheers everyone
have a great time
[Music]